December 17th, Stellar Year 2144
Brother...
July 27th, Stellar Year 2148
It's so hot!
Stop it! You'll make me feel hot, too!
It's hot, though.
Summer's here.
I'm taking my clothes off!
No, you aren't!
You know the saying,
"Shinto mekkyaku sureba" or whatever.
That sounds like something Kaie would say.
"Shinto mekkyaku"?
This is the spot!
Where we went to look at
the flowers! I remember!
We did it right after we got deployed here!
Would you like to dance again, Anju?
We're just about to start a battle, Daiya.
Okay...
April 5th, Stellar Year 2148
I'm from Luskinia.
I was with Shin before, too.
Set it there.
Got it.
What unit are you from?
Scale. You?
Luskinia.
And you, Mr. Daiya?
Just call me "Daiya." Claymore, in my case.
And what year are you in?
Fourth year.
Same as me.
Most people here are fourth-years.
That's the one thing
that's equal about all of us.
Hey, any girls you've got your eye on?
You're asking that after we just met?
Her, maybe? You two seemed close!
No! I'm not telling.
Why? You like keeping secrets?
No more secrets from anyone.
That's right. Daiya does nothing
but stare at Anju all day.
It's obvious he likes her.
You guys seem to be having fun.
Daiya, you're embarrassing us.
Shut up and help!
Hey, Daiya says he wants to talk to Anju!
Theo?
Please, no!
Did you call me, Daiya?
No, it's not like that.
Then what's it like?
Well, it's just kind of a sausage-fest
over here, so I thought it...
Hey, speaking of sausage-fests,
I heard the craziest thing.
What?
There's some rich girl
who's working as a Handler.
Wow, sounds interesting! Tell me more!
She's obviously a really hot pig princess!
With huge tits, too!
Since she's a pig, after all.
She's a white pig. It's only natural.
Like this?
I could see her with a
big pink rose on her back!
And I bet she talks
all prim and proper, too.
She'll greet you with,
"And a fine morning to you!"
And says "very well" instead of "yes."
I can tell you for sure
I'd snap at her in the first 30 seconds.
No, we don't know that.
She may be a frail little girl who's never held
anything heavier than a knitting needle.
She can't handle wind or rain,
and she'll wilt in too much sunlight.
Like that?
Are you talking about a soldier?
If she was mumbling at me
in a thin, frail voice,
I'd get pretty annoyed.
Guys, calm down.
She's just some ugly woman who has to work
'cause she couldn't get married.
What? She's obviously a goddess.
She's descended to the land of mortals
to save us poor Eighty-Six.
Well, I don't know if she's a
kind princess or a goddess, but...
But I'd like to meet her someday,
if she really exists.
Well, I can tell you
she's not either of those.
She's a white pig, at the end of the day.
Right?
Anju!
Daiya...
Commander! Are they drunk?
I don't know.
There's nothing in those cups but water, right?
It's water, yeah.
But, well, they look like they're having fun.
I think it's okay.
You mean you don't care.
People can tell things like that.
I guess so.
Originally, people who were going off to battle
hated the cherry blossoms.
The flowers have a short lifespan.
They all bloom at the same time
and fall at the same time.
They leave the branches behind easily,
as if there's nothing holding them back at all.
But I like the way they're so bold.
Look, I made it my mark.
What's your mark?
There's a story behind it, right?
I think so.
You think?
It wasn't mine to begin with.
Hey, you two lovebirds!
You need to enjoy yourselves
while you've got the chance!
If you can't laugh anymore, you lose, right?
Right!
Yeah.
I was worried there might be a Legion attack
while we were out here.
I'm glad there wasn't.
I told you! He can always tell!
He's the headless Reaper
of the Eastern Front.
I heard the rumors,
but I guess they're true.
I heard you're looking for your missing head.
If I pull that scarf off, then...
Do you not have a head?
That's why the skeleton mark has no head!
I get it!
Well, let's make
the next six months good ones, Reaper.
Glad to have you!
Gwad to hawve you...
Yeah, me too, Shin.
"Reaper."
You, too.
You're sure popular.
I'm counting on you.
That's not like you at all.
Is it going to rain?
Shooting stars!
No way! No way!
Shooting stars?
Where?
Don't go chasing after them.
You're not a kid!
Me, too!
It's been four months since then, huh?
There are a lot of fewer of us.
The only number that hasn't gone down
is the one on Kujo's blackboard.
I wish time would just stop.
That'd be nice.
I'm afraid it won't for the next two months.
Sorry I'm late.
Beginning coordination mission.
Um, Captain, today...
Oh, are you scared, Major?
If you're scared, why not quit?
Major, if it's too much, you don't have to.
I'm fine!
I'll do what I can until the very end!
Got it.
Skorpions. Incoming artillery fire.
They really are in the way!
Wait, are those the Skorpions
from the next unit over?
There are just too many of them!
They've learned that we can
anticipate their routes and ambush them.
So they start by blasting
every hiding spot with artillery
and then finish us off with the Löwe
when we're flushed out, huh?
That's a lot of effort for a bunch of guys
in aluminum coffins like us.
I'm so happy I could cry!
If only we could use mortars...
Burnt Tail!
Can someone from the Sixth Platoon go?
Not now, with all that artillery fire...
With this landscape, if we go now...
Daiya, wait!
I'm fine!
Black Dog, get away from there!
Black Dog!
Anju...
I can go now, Burnt Tail!
I can aim from above!
They'll just shoot back at you, Gunslinger.
Laughing Fox, can you circle downstream
and come back up?
The March Hare could, but...
I'm not ending up a hunk of scrap metal.
Make it in time!
I'm counting on you,
Reaper.
Burnt Tail!
Burnt Tail...
Damn it...
March Hare, come back.
Snow Witch, take over command from Black Dog.
Can you do it?
Yes, leave it to me.
Major.
Yes.
If I told you to cut your Para-RAID,
would you?
Is that...
You've never seen a person get shot, right?
What do you mean?
I can't let Daiya become a Legion.
If you think you can't handle it,
just cut the link.
No...
This is all I can do,
but it's my responsibility as a Handler.
Thank you for the meal.
I'll carry that.
I'm fine. It's light.
I'm just fine.
Really?
Really, I can carry it myself.
Right, Kitty?
Let's play darts.
We finally lost Daiya and Lecca, too, huh?
Here, it's just a question
of when it happens.
Yeah.
You'll still fight,
even if you're the last one left.
Until you make a grave for that...
For your brother, huh?
It's all I can do.
My brother hasn't forgiven me.
He still blames me. So...
He's obsessed with his brother's head.
I guess you really are a Reaper
in search of a missing head.
Shin.
It's your fault.
Everything. It's all your fault!
That Mom and Dad died.
The fact that I'm about to die.
It's all...
All because of your sin!
Shin!
It's good.
Thanks, Annette.
Is this a real egg?
Artificial.
The strawberries are real.
Sorry, there wasn't time.
July 27th, Stellar Year 2148
No, it's fine.
I'm glad you came, though.
Happy birthday, Lena.
But your present was delivered yesterday.
Oh, you got it?
Why a rocking chair?
"Why"?
Well, you know...
I thought it'd be nice.
Well, actually, Nicolaus gave it to me,
but I'm not going to use it.
It seemed like someone older picked it, yeah.
But you've looked like
you need more sleep lately.
It's perfect for a nap, huh?
Annette, you always end up with guys
who are in the wrong age range.
Well, all the guys my age...
Not a chance.
They're too childish.
So, what happened?
You came to ask me something, right?
Hey, Annette.
What is it?
Just hypothetically,
if the Para-RAIDs had some kind
of effect on a person's mind...
Oh, then it'd go "pop."
We'd pop the Processor's skull right open
and do a thorough exam of their brain.
Just like we were gonna do with Undertaker.
And when it was done,
we'd just throw it away.
For a Handler, we'd immediately
give them a thorough exam,
and then transfer them to another unit.
Sorry, I have to go.
Leave the cake.
I'll come back and eat it later.
Lena?
I'll make the usual cake next year.
This was just fine.
Thanks.
I can't let Daiya become part of the Legion.
Captain Nouzen has been doing that for years,
to keep his comrades
from becoming part of the Legion.
July 28th, Stellar Year 2148
Two Processors died in the last battle.
One was mortally wounded,
but it was his combat commander,
not the Legion, who dealt the killing blow.
How many machines do we have left?
Sixteen people.
Our military's mortars have a range
close to that of the Skorpion's howitzers.
We can use them to provide support
at the front lines
and save the lives of the Eighty-Six.
No, we can lessen attrition at the front lines
and defend the nation more efficiently.
Mortars need to be reloaded after firing.
And they're set up
in the middle of a minefield.
It's too close to the front lines.
You're telling us
to take that risk for the Eighty-Six?
Eighty-Six can be replaced,
but Republic soldiers can't.
I can't authorize their use.
Both the military and the people
want a homeland defense
that's technologically advanced and ethical,
with zero casualties.
And the military's job is
to follow the will of the people.
But...
Lena, how many times do I have to tell you?
Stop siding with the Eighty-Six.
But, they're human...
They must be suffering.
I have another mission for the Spearheads, actually.
A new Legion base has been confirmed
to be under construction near their area.
As soon as they're ready,
they are to advance immediately
on the base and destroy it.
Wait, even before replacing the ones they lost?
Why don't we get new replacements,
like the other units?
This base exists to support the
Legion in their advance.
If it's not taken out now, before it's built,
it'll be Spearhead that suffers.
You want to save them, right, Major Milizé?
Or am I wrong?
Understood, sir.
This concludes the mission briefing.
Understood.
I'm sorry.
I know you don't even have replacements
for your casualties yet,
and we're already sending
you on a new mission.
It's nothing new.
We're aware of the Legion base as well.
It's almost certainly a trap.
You know it's a trap,
and yet you'll attack anyway?
It may be more dangerous to leave it there.
I wish we could've used the
mortars to provide support.
But I couldn't get authorization.
Oh, those things?
I've never seen them used.
I'd be surprised if they still worked.
Is that so?
Don't worry about it.
We weren't counting on them to begin with.
Stress is bad for your skin!
Yeah.
That's all for today, then.
Try to get some rest tonight, okay?
Right, right.
Goodnight!
Bye!
Night.
Captain?
Major, are you okay?
Your voice sounds a little on edge.
Make sure you get some rest tonight.
Okay...
You can get sweets inside the walls, right?
Why not eat some and take a break?
What is it?
No...
You just sounded like your brother.
He gave me chocolate when things were bad.
You really are brothers, huh?
It's far worse for you than it is for me.
You must like sweets too,
right, Captain Nouzen?
Yes. Did my brother say that?
Yes.
What was his expression when he said it?
Was he smiling?
Yes.
He had such kind eyes.
I remember them really well.
I'm impressed you remember.
It's an important memory for me.
I'll never forget it.
Of course, this time I spend talking
to you is very important as well.
Major?
O-Okay, goodnight!
Goodnight.
I won't forget.
"Will You Remember Me?"